housewifefuck.com 2011-06-30

# Privacy | Pornstar Vid - Video on Demand

**AEBN Privacy Policy**

AEBN has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering practices for all of AEBN websites.

AEBN has established a privacy policy with the mission of building member trust and confidence by promoting the use of fair information practices. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [billing@aebn.net](mailto:billing@aebn.net). 

**This Theater is owned and operated by: AEBN**   
AEBN   
500 Archdale drive   
Charlotte, NC 28217   
Phone: 1.704.529.1600   
Customer Service Department: 1.800.628.0241   

**Cookies**

AEBN uses session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. For more information on cookies [click here](http://www.howstuffworks.com/cookie.htm).

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as username and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user special offers and updates from AEBN. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the person when necessary. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

As an individual, you have the opportunity to limit the personal information you provide. We provide you with the opportunity to 'opt out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt out of receiving them by contacting us at 704.529.1600, [billing@aebn.net](mailto:billing@aebn.net) or 500 Archdale Drive Charlotte NC, 28217.

**_Information Collection & Use_**

**Registration**   
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information including your name and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

AEBN is the sole owner of the information collected on www.aebn.net. AEBN collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Access to Personally Identifiable Information   
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, emailing our Customer Support at [billing@aebn.net](mailto:billing@aebn.net), or contacting us by telephone or postal mail using the information located at the top of this page.

**Surveys or Contests**   
From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, monitor site traffic, personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), and send participants an email newsletter.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**Tell-A-Friend**   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. AEBN stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [billing@aebn.net](mailto:billing@aebn.net) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**_Uses of Information_**

**Email**   
AEBN members and affiliates receive periodic email notices that include exclusive special offers and information about sales, promotions, new releases, and other relevant information. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out by contacting us at 704.529.1600, [billing@aebn.net](mailto:billing@aebn.net) or 500 Archdale Drive Charlotte NC, 28217.

**Non-personal information**   
Like many web sites, we collect and analyze standard log file information and Session ID information to analyze site traffic, improve site performance, and prevent fraud. Session IDs are bits of code on your computer that assist your browser in navigating our site. We do not associate personal information with log file information or cookies, except when needed to prevent fraud.

**Affiliate and Webmaster sign-up**   
AEBN collects prospective affiliate and webmaster contact information to process applications and conduct business. This information includes: name, checks payable, address, city, state/province, country, minimum payout, password, source of referral, tax ID (EIN or social security number for U.S. residents), and date of birth.

**Legal Disclaimer**   
AEBN reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.

The AEBN web site(s) contains links to other sites. AEBN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Our site uses a secure online ordering system that enables clients to purchase minutes for viewing movies online, as well as rent and download movies. AEBN collects users financial information, such as account and credit card numbers, for verification purposes only. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services, and never for any other reason. 

**Security**   
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link: [Verisign](http://www.verisign.com/ssl/ssl-information-center/index.html). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of online transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our web site, you can email us at [billing@aebn.net](mailto:billing@aebn.net)

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
